<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KoDa Cast</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on KoDa Cast</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:33:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ep 1, Koi Ponds</title><link>/episode/1-koi-ponds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/episode/1-koi-ponds/</guid><description>KOI Ponds - Introduction to the KoDa Cast health informatics podcast, including discussions on the KOI Pond, on the value of the physician informatician, and jankiness scales.</description></item><item><title>John Manning</title><link>/host/johnmanning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 23:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/host/johnmanning/</guid><description>Dr. Manning is an innovative, usability-focused informatician developer with skills in design and video editing. He is double-boarded in Emergency Medicine and Clinical Informatics; practices clinically at Atrium Health; and educates medical students / residents at the bedside (Assistant Professor). He was also one of the founding board members of AMIA Clinical Informatics Fellows (ACIF) and served as their first secretary during his fellowship.
Dr. Manning specializes in teaching Flutter development and its specific applications within healthcare.</description></item><item><title>Mike Wang</title><link>/host/mikewang/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 23:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>/host/mikewang/</guid><description>Michael Wang is an assistant professor at the University of California, San Francisco where he is an academic hospitalist and clinical informaticist. He has been involved in health IT dating back to high school in 1997 when he made a Microsoft Access database to track hepatitis C patients. As a developer, physician, and burgeoning data scientist, he sees the immense potential of FHIR to fast track mobilization of clinical data to accelerate both clinical and operational data-driven decision making.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>A podcast created by practicing clinical informaticians who love talking about medicine, technology and everything bordering or in between. Our content is specifically targeted at prospective or early career clinical informaticians&amp;hellip;but is intended to be relevant for developers interested in building for healthcare or clinicians who are just curious about how technology can improve their everyday practice. We are constantly revising our content so please let us know if there is anything you want us to talk about!</description></item><item><title>Cookie Policy</title><link>/cookie-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cookie-policy/</guid><description>This cookie policy (&amp;ldquo;Policy&amp;rdquo;) describes what cookies are and how and they&amp;rsquo;re being used by the kodacast.com website (&amp;ldquo;Website&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;) and any of its related products and services (collectively, &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;). This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you (&amp;ldquo;User&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;rdquo;) and this Website operator (&amp;ldquo;Operator&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;). You should read this Policy so you can understand the types of cookies we use, the information we collect using cookies and how that information is used.</description></item><item><title>Not Found (404)</title><link>/404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/404/</guid><description>Sorry, but I cannot find what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>This privacy policy (&amp;ldquo;Policy&amp;rdquo;) describes how the personally identifiable information (&amp;ldquo;Personal Information&amp;rdquo;) you may provide on the kodacast.com website (&amp;ldquo;Website&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;) and any of its related products and services (collectively, &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;) is collected, protected and used. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you (&amp;ldquo;User&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;your&amp;rdquo;) and this Website operator (&amp;ldquo;Operator&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/search/</guid><description>Nothing on this page will be visible. This file exists solely to respond to /search URL.
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.</description></item></channel></rss>